<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>health on slash blog</title><link>/tags/health/</link><description>Recent content in health on slash blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Patrick O'Doherty :: CC-BY</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 15:18:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Running, reading, blue hair, and orbital mechanics</title><link>/2015/06/14/running-reading-blue-hair-and-orbital-mechanics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 15:18:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2015/06/14/running-reading-blue-hair-and-orbital-mechanics/</guid><description>I've lapsed yet again in the weekly writing requirement of the Iron Blogger project at Noisebridge and so feel compelled to give a core-dump type post to recount the happenings of the last two weeks.
I made a real breakthrough in my running in the last two weeks, after picking out some advice from /r/running on Reddit. I was absentmindedly browsing looking for training plans when I came upon a &amp;ldquo;beginners guide&amp;rdquo; of sorts which I scrolled though.</description></item><item><title>Cycling bikes is fun</title><link>/2015/03/25/cycling-bikes-is-fun/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 20:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2015/03/25/cycling-bikes-is-fun/</guid><description>I started riding my bike to work the other day, and it's very enjoyable. I've been feeling a bit sedentary in recent times, so a more active morning and evening commute is a really welcome change. I'd kinda forgotten that nice feeling you get post-exercise, and it's made me realise that I should do this more often.
I find it easy to fill time with non-exercise related things, so coupling exercise with my daily commute will hopefully facilitate this becoming a habit.</description></item><item><title>2015: Resolutions</title><link>/2015/01/01/2015-resolutions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 14:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>/2015/01/01/2015-resolutions/</guid><description>As I write this I'm back in Dublin having been at 31C3 these last few days. It was a fantastic time meeting a whole range of new interesting people, as well as getting to know better the wonderful friends that I've made this year.
Running into the end of the year I was feeling a little burnt out, mostly due to fire-fighting interpersonal drama in Noisebridge. I was very much looking forward to the break from SF and the commitments I have there in the hopes that I'd be re-energised, and as it turns out it has done exactly that.</description></item></channel></rss>